

SUMMARY

Creative and professional back-end developer with 6+ years of experience in building and maintaining web services. Proficient in Linux, PHP, Python, modern frameworks and libraries, web servers administration and testing.

Developed and maintaind over 10 international projects.

HARD SKILLS

PHP, Laravel
Python, Django, Flask
MySQL
Docker, Docker-compose
Git
Linux
PhpUnit, Selenium

SOFT SKILS

Adaptability Problem-solving Work ethic Positivity Responsibility

Maksym Chechkov

BACKEND DEVELOPER

Ukraine, Odessa

- +380 (63) 429-00-19
- max.chechkov@protonmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/max-chechkov

WORK EXPERIENCE

Middle-Senior PHP developer

Hertz TOV. Ukraine | Mar. 2020 - Present

- Implement enhancements to improve web functionality and responsiveness
- Redevelop existing systems to support custom account management, content and mobile apps back-end
- Optimizing database queries
- Design and development of web services
- Integration with other products and services of the company

Junior-Middle PHP developer

WebMagic. Ukraine | Sep. 2016 - Jan. 2020

- Development and maintenance of e-commerce projects
- Writing and automating Unit tests, acceptance tests
- Containerization of projects by using Docker / Docker-compose

EDUCATION

Kharkiv National Pedagogical University

Teacher - choreographer | 2004 - 2009

COURSES

Hillel IT School Python | 2021